I am always deeply honored that folks want to hear my insights, want to hear me speak,
want to be inspired through my words and my conviction and my passion.
However, I am constantly asked by various organizations and institutions to do this for free.
Now, this is not about capitalism because I'm not looking to exploit.
However, I am a merchant of my own gifts and my own skills.
When you see jingles saying, I sang them and recorded them.
When you see my videos posted, I edited them.
When you see my graphics posted, I designed them.
When you see artwork being sold, I drew that.
This on a creative level is just me.
And the way that I support myself is not through employment or investment or sponsorship.
I support myself by literally peddling my wares, whether it is my art on Amanda Land exports, whether it is my content on Patreon, whether it is my skill set in the world.
So it is highly disrespectful to continuously be asked to come and speak from the heart.
This would be a completely valid ask where I still in Hollywood with a primary career.
However, that is no longer the case.
I am solely supported by y'all.
That's it.
I am an independent, artistic intellectual.
I create art that edutains in a multiple set of mediums.
And it is you all support of that, that allows me to continue to create art that edutains.
In the space of community, it is going to require us to figure out ways to show up in value beyond simply just money.
And this is us thinking outside of capitalism.
However, it is imperative that we figure out what barter options there are, that we identify ways that we can be in symbiosis with folks versus simply in ask.
And that is what's going to help train us on how to exist together.
So again, thank you for valuing my voice and my mind.
Also understand that my voice and my mind are things that I have cultivated.
They are seeds that I have sown.
And they are my harvest.
And I don't think I should be asked consistently by organizations and institutions to give them away for free.
Not your brand, so you should name them, name them!